

PROFILE

Adaptable, self-starting, and passionate team player with 10 years of business and accounting experience seeking an opportunity to provide dedicated, detail-oriented support in a fast-paced work environment that aligns with personal values while focusing on professional and team success. Looking to enter tech field and expand growth opportunities.

CONTACT

PHONE:

425-623-7074

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/michaelbrenckle

EMAIL:

brenckle@gmail.com

EDUCATION

WGU - Bachelor of Science, Information Technology (currently enrolled)

MICHAEL BRENCKLE

EXPERIENCED BOOKKEEPER & ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

QUALIFICATIONS

- Registered for IT Specialist Program (A+, Network+, Security+)
- Enrolled at WGU for B.S., Information Technology
- Registered/insured car w/ immaculate driving record
- Certified Full-Charge Bookkeeper

WORK EXPERIENCE

North Star Tax & Accounting – Account Manager

August 2019 – March 2021 (laid off due to COVID)

- Full-Charge day-to-day bookkeeping for a diverse set of clients in a wide range of industries
- Monthly review and financial statement preparation
- QuickBooks Online and Desktop experience

PROJECTLINE/YESLER - Accounting Associate & Payroll Manager

November 2011 – June 2018

- Responsible for employee on-boarding, benefit administration, and HRIS management
- Handled day-to-day bookkeeping tasks and multi-state payroll functions for over 300 employees in the US, UK, and Canada
- ADP, Paychex, and Intacct ERP experience
- Direct report to CFO, supported Controller and HR Director

MORE POWER RACING - Store Manager

August 2008 – November 2011

- Managed customer support and vendor relationships
- Handled day-to-day bookkeeping tasks
- Supervised warehouse staff and inventory systems
- Website administration, including HTML development and graphic design
- Executive Assistant to CEO/President, Lead Training Manager